They don't care for it
if you stare at them and hyperventilate.
Sadly, that's my home-run swing.
(Leonard:)Look, everything went fine.
(Leonard:)I didn't even have to refer
to my impromptu conversation starters.
That woman across the hall is into me.
(Howard:)Let's go to the tape.
(Howard:)Look at her reaction
to the good-night kiss.
(Howard:)No change in respiration, pupils undilated,
no flushing of the chest.
Nice close-up, by the way.
(Sheldon:)Interesting. Her jaws are clenched.
No tongue access.
(Sheldon:)Clearly a bad sign
amongst mating humans.
(Leonard:)That's not a bad sign.
(Sheldon:)Please. You might as well have been
two iguana with no dewlap enlargement.
(Raj:)And the worst sign of all
is you're here and not there.
(Leonard:)I'm not there,
because I'm taking things slow.
(Leonard:)Which, by the way, compared to you guys,
approaches warp speed.
(Leonard:)And take down that camera.
(Raj:)He was a lot more fun
when he had no hope.
(Howard:)Give him time.